There are close to 58,000 homeless people in Los Angeles County.
洛杉矶县有近58,000名无家可归者。
That’s a shocking and tragic number for a region that’s home to some of the richest people in the world.
对于一个住着一些世界顶级富豪的地区来说，这个数字令人震惊，也令人痛心。
At last, the problem became so acute—and so visible—that Los Angeles took extraordinary action.
这个问题终于变得如此严重，也如此显眼，以至于洛杉矶采取了非同寻常的行动。
The citizens of this county voted in November 2016 and again in March 2017 to raise their own taxes.
该县公民于2016年11月投票、2017年3月再次投票，决定给自己加税。
The purpose of such action is to fund an enormous multibillion-dollar 10-year program of housing and social services for the homeless.
此举的目的是资助一项为期10年、耗资数十亿美元的庞大计划，为无家可归者提供住房和社会服务。
As a result, Los Angeles now has its best chance in decades to combat homelessness.
因此，洛杉矶如今迎来了几十年来应对无家可归问题的最好机会。
This is an opportunity that surely all can agree must not be wasted.
这个机会绝不能浪费，想必所有人都能认同这一点。
It is neither desirable nor morally acceptable nor practical for this county to tolerate the signs of deprivation more commonly associated with the slums of Rio de Janeiro.
该县若容忍那些更常与里约热内卢贫民窟联系在一起的贫困景象，既不可取，在道德上也无法接受，而且不切实际。
How did we get here?
我们是怎么走到这一步的？
For as long as there have been homeless people, there has been a tendency to blame the victims themselves for their condition—to see their failure to thrive as an issue of character, of moral weakness, of laziness.
自从有了无家可归者，人们就一直倾向于把他们的处境归咎于这些受害者自己，把他们没能过上好日子看作品格问题，看作道德软弱和懒惰。
But contrary to popular belief, the homeless in Los Angeles are not mostly mentally ill or drug addicted or frightening, although a sizable minority meet some of those descriptions.
但与普遍看法相反，洛杉矶的无家可归者大多并没有精神疾病，也不吸毒成瘾，也不吓人，尽管确有为数不少的少数人符合上述某些情况。
Today, a greater and greater proportion of people living on the streets are there because of bad luck or a series of mistakes, or because the economy forgot them—they lost a job or were evicted or fled an abusive marriage just as the housing market was growing increasingly unforgiving.
如今，露宿街头的人中，有越来越大比例的人落到这一步，是因为运气不好或一连串失误，或者是因为经济把他们遗忘了——他们丢了工作，或被逐出住所，或为摆脱虐待而逃离了婚姻，而恰在此时，住房市场正变得越来越严酷。
The challenges are enormous, even if everyone is pulling in the same direction.
即便所有人都劲往一处使，面临的挑战也依然巨大。
That reality was driven home this month by a new Los Angeles Homeless Services Authority report showing that the county’s homeless population is growing faster than the supply of new housing.
本月，洛杉矶无家可归者服务管理局的一份新报告显示，该县无家可归人口的增长速度超过了新住房的供应速度，让人们深刻认识到了这一现实。
In the world’s richest nation, homelessness on this scale should be shameful and shocking.
在世界上最富有的国家，如此规模的无家可归现象理应令人羞愧和震惊。
But most Los Angeles residents are no longer either shocked or shamed.
但大多数洛杉矶居民已不再感到震惊，也不再感到羞愧。
Increasingly, we are uncomfortable, annoyed, disgusted, scared or unaware.
我们越来越感到不自在、恼火、厌恶、害怕，或者对此浑然不觉。
Compassion is being replaced by resignation.
同情心正在被听天由命的心态取代。